{
    "id": "8a162359f07d460a89c4e72b0d376fa8",
    "title": "Intransitive Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The car …………………….. on the way to work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "broke down",
                "broke off",
                "broke away"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c25b88848192485fb3ac772ae6a34ba9"
        },
        {
            "question": "All songs in that film are …………………….. with youngsters.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "catching on",
                "catching up",
                "catching off"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "be265f66e83b4596b62144afd4a9bd12"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t want to …………………….. here ever again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "come back",
                "come in",
                "come on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "67227786837945399f9405d7ef8f6773"
        },
        {
            "question": "The thieves must have …………………….. through the back door.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "come on",
                "come in",
                "come up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "72c3ab0edd794c6ab065a244750b3250"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was hit hard on the head, but …………………….. again after a few minutes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "came off",
                "came at",
                "came to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "060af58fa78a4228b2950e675faaf504"
        },
        {
            "question": "Julie had promised to …………………….., but she never did.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "come in",
                "come up",
                "come over"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "209034a24a0747a787ef814333bd9b6f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I absolutely like it when old friends ……………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "drop at",
                "drop by",
                "drop off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "83aa5633ea614225a2a00456743d7938"
        },
        {
            "question": "He earns just enough to ……………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "get by",
                "get away",
                "get off"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c5dcbcfb948644aa851116b83522a5ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "Granny tried to …………………….., but she couldn’t do it on her own.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "get on",
                "get up",
                "get to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6eafa2d871694130b96375a9aea183a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t want to …………………. to that country ever again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go back",
                "go away",
                "go in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a09b34a9153f447199d23f39ebfb22e7"
        }
    ]
}